<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project name="usage" basedir=".">
  <target name="usage">
        <echo>
            TARGETS

            DEPLOYMENT:
            all/deploy/install: Deploys entire target
               pre-deploy (test if not production) advance-build restart 
            revert: revert-build restart
            pre-deploy: Deploys entire WEB-INF environment to the pre-build directories
            advance-build: Moves the prebuild directory to current
            revert-build: Moves the post-build directory to current, but does not restart
            gwt: Compile gwt targets to the pre-directory
            jsp-compile: Precompile jsp files and generate appropriate web.xml servlert reference

            PROPERTIES:
            createEnum: Rebuild java class ZfinPropertiesEnum.
            createPropertiesFiles: Creates TT file (createTTFile) and env file (createEnvFile) for given INSTANCE.
            exportAllInstances: Exports all instances defined by instances.properties.

            DEVELOPMENT:
            dirtydeploy: Deploys entire WEB-INF environment changes without cleaning
            dirty-gwt: Deploys all gwt instances into the active target directory
            do: Clean, compile and build entire WEB-INF environment. No copying into target directory
            clean: Cleans WEB-INF target
            compile: Compile WEB-INF target only
            runHibernate: Run the HibernateStandaloneUtil class to check your Persistence

            UTILITIES:
            deploy-javadoc: Create the JavaDoc and deploy it into the targetroot
            build-properties:  Echos important build-propertiets.
            echoProps: Print out all java properties
            jversion: Print out the used JVM
            javadocs: Create JavaDoc for ZFIN API
            generate-wsdl-doi-client: Generates wsdl java client code for the DOI
            graph:  Generates dotty graph.

            TOMCAT:
            tomcat-restart: Restarts tomcat
            tomcat-start: Start tomcat
            tomcat-debug-start: Start tomcat and allow remote debugging on port $JPDA_ADDRESS
            tomcat-stop: Stop tomcat
            tomcat-kill: Forced tomcat stop
            deploy-catalina-base: Build/update tomcat instance in CATALINA_BASE
                (used to be called create-mutant-instance)

            TESTS:
            test: Always run this before comitting. Seriously.
                (currently just points to runtests-quiet)
            unittests: Runs non-db test suites in org.zfin.UnitTests
            runDBtests: Runs db test suites in org.zfin.DbUnitTests
            runBlasttests: Runs db and blast test suites combined in org.zfin.sequence.blast.BlastAndDBTests
            blastStressTest: Runs a blast stress test.
            enumtests: Tests only enumerations against the database
            smokeTests:   Tests via http requests against our site.
            serviceTests: Tests third-party service connections.
            runtests-quiet: Runs all test suites in org.zfin.UnitTests but only gives a summary
            compile-tests: Compiles test directories
            runTagTests: Compiles and deploys all tag-unit-testing code into a separate application 
                root directory.  Deploys it into an app server root directory specified by the 
                environment variable TAGUNIT_HOME
            blastHeuristics:  Runs full blast heuristics to determine the optimal blast setting.
	    runBlasttests: Runs all blast tests; have to have ssh keys to genomix set up in order to run these from ant deploy.
        </echo>
    </target>

</project>
